{
  "question1": {
    "question": "How many threads does Dart/Flutter run on??",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "Multiple"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  "question2": {
    "question": "Best way to animate things in flutter is: ",
    "answers": [
      "Using stateful widget and updating setState()",
      "AnimationBuilder widget",
      "Flutter has no animations, external library",
      "Use gifs"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  "question3": {
    "question": "How to make property private in Dart?",
    "answers": [
      "private var property;",
      "var property",
      "var $property",
      "var _property"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  "question4": {
    "question": "Who created Dart?",
    "answers": [
      "Amazon",
      "Google",
      "Apple",
      "Oracle"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  "question5": {
    "question": "Which doesn't describe an anonymous method?",
    "answers": [
      "() {}",
      "(int myValue) => 0;",
      "() {} => 0;",
      "(int k){ return 0;}"

    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  "question6": {
    "question": "Where flutter app's can be run?",
    "answers": [
      "iOS and Web",
      "Android & iOS",
      "Android & Desktop",
      "All of mentioned"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  "question7": {
    "question": "How is '...' operator called?",
    "answers": [
      "There is no '...' operator",
      "Mapping",
      "Spread",
      "Varargs"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  "question8": {
    "question": "What are build modes in Flutter?",
    "answers": [
      "Debug, Compile, Package",
      "Compile, Package, Run",
      "Debug, Package, Release ",
      "Debug, Profile, Release"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  "question9": {
    "question": "What's true about hot reload and hot restart?",
    "answers": [
      "hot reload: faster, hot restart: saves  state",
      "hot restart: faster and saves  state",
      "hot reload: faster and saves  state",
      "hot restart: faster, hot reload: saves  state"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  "question10": {
    "question": "What is BLoC",
    "answers": [
      "Business Logic Controller",
      "Business Logic Class",
      "Business Logic Component",
      "Business Logic Construction"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  } ,
  "question11": {
    "question": "What is null-aware operation?",
    "answers": [
      "checking if value is not null before using it",
      "replacing existing value with another different than null",
      "assigning a value to a variable only when current is null",
      "there is nothing like this"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  }
}